https://smoca.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to Navigation
Skip to Content
Scottsdale Center For The Performing ArtsSMoCAPublic ArtLearning & InnovationScottsdale Arts FestivalCanal Convergence
SUPPORT THE ARTS IN SCOTTSDALE
Art inspires and sustains us. We look to you, our community of arts lovers, for help in this critical moment. Please consider becoming a ONE Member or giving a donation today to support the arts in Scottsdale.
Give Now
Scottsdale Center For The Performing ArtsSMoCAPublic ArtLearning & InnovationScottsdale Arts FestivalCanal Convergence
Shop Online Today!
Shop Online Today!
This Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on
the collection, use and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service
and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You.
We use Your Personal data to provide and improve the
Service. By using the Service, You agree to the collection and use of
information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Interpretation and Definitions
Interpretation
The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have
meanings defined under the following conditions.
The following definitions shall have the same meaning
regardless of whether they appear in singular or in plural.
Definitions
For the purposes of this Privacy Policy:
You
means the individual accessing or using the Service, or the company, or other
legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or using the
Service, as applicable.
Under GDPR (General Data Protection
Regulation), You can be referred to as the Data Subject or as the User as you
are the individual using the Service.
Company
(referred to as either “the Company”, “We”, “Us”
or “Our” in this Agreement) refers to Scottsdale Arts, 7380 East
Second St, Scottsdale, AZ 85251.
For the purpose of the GDPR, the Company is
the Data Controller.
Affiliate
means an entity that controls, is controlled by or is under common control with
a party, where “control” means ownership of 50% or more of the
shares, equity interest or other securities entitled to vote for election of
directors or other managing authority.Account
means a unique account created for You to access our Service or parts of our
Service.Website
refers to Scottsdale Arts, accessible from https://scottsdalearts.org/Service
refers to the Website.Country
refers to: Arizona, United States
Service
Provider means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf
of the Company. It refers to third-party companies or individuals employed by
the Company to facilitate the Service, to provide the Service on behalf of the
Company, to perform services related to the Service or to assist the Company in
analyzing how the Service is used.
For the purpose of the GDPR, Service
Providers are considered Data Processors.
Third-party
Social Media Service refers to any website or any social network website
through which a User can log in or create an account to use the Service.
Personal
Data is any information that relates to an identified or identifiable
individual.
For the purposes for GDPR, Personal Data
means any information relating to You such as a name, an identification number,
location data, online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the
physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social
identity.
For the purposes of the CCPA, Personal Data
means any information that identifies, relates to, describes or is capable of
being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly,
with You.
Cookies
are small files that are placed on Your computer, mobile device or any other
device by a website, containing the details of Your browsing history on that
website among its many uses.Usage
Data refers to data collected automatically, either generated by the use of
the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the
duration of a page visit).Data
Controller, for the purposes of the GDPR (General Data Protection
Regulation), refers to the Company as the legal person which alone or jointly
with others determines the purposes and means of the processing of Personal
Data.Do Not
Track (DNT) is a concept that has been promoted by US regulatory
authorities, in particular the U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC), for the
Internet industry to develop and implement a mechanism for allowing internet
users to control the tracking of their online activities across websites.Business,
for the purpose of the CCPA (California Consumer Privacy Act), refers to the
Company as the legal entity that collects Consumers’ personal information and
determines the purposes and means of the processing of Consumers’ personal
information, or on behalf of which such information is collected and that
alone, or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the
processing of consumers’ personal information, that does business in the State
of California.Consumer,
for the purpose of the CCPA (California Consumer Privacy Act), means a natural
person who is a California resident. A resident, as defined in the law,
includes (1) every individual who is in the USA for other than a temporary or
transitory purpose, and (2) every individual who is domiciled in the USA who is
outside the USA for a temporary or transitory purpose.Sale,
for the purpose of the CCPA (California Consumer Privacy Act), means selling,
renting, releasing, disclosing, disseminating, making available, transferring,
or otherwise communicating orally, in writing, or by electronic or other means,
a Consumer’s Personal information to another business or a third party for
monetary or other valuable consideration.
Collecting and Using Your Personal Data
Types of Data Collected
Personal Data
While using Our Service, We may ask You to provide Us with
certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or
identify You. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited
to:
Email addressFirst name and last namePhone numberAddress, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, CityUsage Data
Usage Data
Usage Data is collected automatically when using the
Service.
Usage Data may include information such as Your Device’s Internet
Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of
our Service that You visit, the time and date of Your visit, the time spent on
those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.
When You access the Service by or through a mobile device,
We may collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited
to, the type of mobile device You use, Your mobile device unique ID, the IP
address of Your mobile device, Your mobile operating system, the type of mobile
Internet browser You use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.
We may also collect information that Your browser sends
whenever You visit our Service or when You access the Service by or through a
mobile device.
Information from Third-Party Social Media Services
The Company allows You to create an account and log in to
use the Service through the following Third-party Social Media Services:
GoogleFacebookTwitter
If You decide to register through or otherwise grant us
access to a Third-Party Social Media Service, We may collect Personal data that
is already associated with Your Third-Party Social Media Service’s account,
such as Your name, Your email address, Your activities or Your contact list
associated with that account.
You may also have the option of sharing additional
information with the Company through Your Third-Party Social Media Service’s
account. If You choose to provide such information and Personal Data, during
registration or otherwise, You are giving the Company permission to use, share,
and store it in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy.
Tracking Technologies and Cookies
We use Cookies and similar tracking technologies to track
the activity on Our Service and store certain information. Tracking technologies
used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to
improve and analyze Our Service.
You can instruct Your browser to refuse all Cookies or to
indicate when a Cookie is being sent. However, if You do not accept Cookies,
You may not be able to use some parts of our Service.
Cookies can be “Persistent” or “Session”
Cookies. Persistent Cookies remain on your personal computer or mobile device
when You go offline, while Session Cookies are deleted as soon as You close
your web browser.
We use both session and persistent Cookies for the purposes
set out below:
provide You with services available through the Website and to enable You to
use some of its features. They help to authenticate users and prevent
fraudulent use of user accounts. Without these Cookies, the services that You
have asked for cannot be provided, and We only use these Cookies to provide You
with those services.
have accepted the use of cookies on the Website.
choices You make when You use the Website, such as remembering your login
details or language preference. The purpose of these Cookies is to provide You
with a more personal experience and to avoid You having to re-enter your
preferences every time You use the Website.
information about traffic to the Website and how users use the Website. The
information gathered via these Cookies may directly or indirectly identify you
as an individual visitor. This is because the information collected is
typically linked to a pseudonymous identifier associated with the device you
use to access the Website. We may also use these Cookies to test new
advertisements, pages, features or new functionality of the Website to see how
our users react to them.
For more information about the cookies we use and your
choices regarding cookies, please visit our Cookies Policy.
Use of Your Personal Data
The Company may use Personal Data for the following
purposes:
To
provide and maintain our Service, including to monitor the usage of our
Service.To manage
Your Account: to manage Your registration as a user of the Service. The
Personal Data You provide can give You access to different functionalities of
the Service that are available to You as a registered user.For the
performance of a contract: the development, compliance and undertaking of
the purchase contract for the products, items or services You have purchased or
of any other contract with Us through the Service.To
contact You: To contact You by email, telephone calls, SMS, or other
equivalent forms of electronic communication, such as a mobile application’s
push notifications regarding updates or informative communications related to
the functionalities, products or contracted services, including the security
updates, when necessary or reasonable for their implementation.To
provide You with news, special offers and general information about other
goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you
have already purchased or enquired about unless You have opted not to receive
such information.To manage
Your requests: To attend and manage Your requests to Us.
We may share your personal information in the following
situations:
With
Service Providers: We may share Your personal information with Service
Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service, to show advertisements
to You to help support and maintain Our Service, to contact You, to advertise
on third party websites to You after You visited our Service or for payment
processing.For
Business transfers: We may share or transfer Your personal information in
connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of Company assets,
financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another
company.With
Affiliates: We may share Your information with Our affiliates, in which
case we will require those affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. Affiliates
include Our parent company and any other subsidiaries, joint venture partners
or other companies that We control or that are under common control with Us.With
Business partners: We may share Your information with Our business partners
to offer You certain products, services or promotions.With
other users: when You share personal information or otherwise interact in
the public areas with other users, such information may be viewed by all users
and may be publicly distributed outside. If You interact with other users or
register through a Third-Party Social Media Service, Your contacts on the
Third-Party Social Media Service may see Your name, profile, pictures and
description of Your activity. Similarly, other users will be able to view
descriptions of Your activity, communicate with You and view Your profile.
Retention of Your Personal Data
The Company will retain Your Personal Data only for as long
as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain
and use Your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal
obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with
applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and
policies.
The Company will also retain Usage Data for internal
analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of
time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve
the functionality of Our Service, or We are legally obligated to retain this
data for longer time periods.
Transfer of Your Personal Data
Your information, including Personal Data, is processed at
the Company’s operating offices and in any other places where the parties
involved in the processing are located. It means that this information may be
transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of Your state,
province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection
laws may differ than those from Your jurisdiction.
Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by Your
submission of such information represents Your agreement to that transfer.
The Company will take all steps reasonably necessary to
ensure that Your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy
Policy and no transfer of Your Personal Data will take place to an organization
or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security
of Your data and other personal information.
Disclosure of Your Personal Data
Business Transactions
If the Company is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset
sale, Your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before Your
Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.
Law enforcement
Under certain circumstances, the Company may be required to
disclose Your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid
requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).
Other legal requirements
The Company may disclose Your Personal Data in the good
faith belief that such action is necessary to:
Comply with a legal obligationProtect and defend the rights or property of the
CompanyPrevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in
connection with the ServiceProtect the personal safety of Users of the
Service or the publicProtect against legal liability
Security of Your Personal Data
The security of Your Personal Data is important to Us, but
remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of
electronic storage is 100% secure. While We strive to use commercially
acceptable means to protect Your Personal Data, We cannot guarantee its
absolute security.
Detailed Information on the Processing of Your Personal Data
Service Providers have access to Your Personal Data only to
perform their tasks on Our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it
for any other purpose.
Analytics
We may use third-party Service providers to monitor and
analyze the use of our Service.
Google
Analytics
Google Analytics is a web analytics service
offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data
collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with
other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualise and
personalise the ads of its own advertising network.
You can opt-out of having made your
activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google
Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics
JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js and dc.js) from sharing information with Google
Analytics about visits activity.
For more information on the privacy practices
of Google, please visit the Google Privacy Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en
Email Marketing
We may use Your Personal Data to contact You with
newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may
be of interest to You. You may opt-out of receiving any, or all, of these
communications from Us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions
provided in any email We send or by contacting Us.
We may use Email Marketing Service Providers to manage and
send emails to You.
Behavioral Remarketing
The Company uses remarketing services to advertise on third
party websites to You after You visited our Service. We and Our third-party
vendors use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on Your past visits
to our Service.
Google
Ads (AdWords)
Google Ads (AdWords) remarketing service is
provided by Google Inc.
You can opt-out of Google Analytics for
Display Advertising and customise the Google Display Network ads by visiting
the Google Ads Settings page: http://www.google.com/settings/ads
Google also recommends installing the
Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on – https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
– for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors
with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google
Analytics.
For more information on the privacy
practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en
Bing
Ads Remarketing
Bing Ads remarketing service is provided by
Microsoft Inc.
You can opt-out of Bing Ads interest-based
ads by following their instructions: https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads
You can learn more about the privacy
practices and policies of Microsoft by visiting their Privacy Policy page: https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/PrivacyStatement
Facebook
Facebook remarketing service is provided by
Facebook Inc.
You can learn more about interest-based
advertising from Facebook by visiting this page: https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950
To opt-out from Facebook’s interest-based
ads, follow these instructions from Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217
Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory
Principles for Online Behavioural Advertising established by the Digital
Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating
companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA http://www.aboutads.info/choices/,
the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada http://youradchoices.ca/ or the European
Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/,
or opt-out using your mobile device settings.
For more information on the privacy practices
of Facebook, please visit Facebook’s Data Policy: https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation
Payments
We may provide paid products and/or services within the
Service. In that case, we may use third-party services for payment processing
(e.g. payment processors).
We will not store or collect Your payment card details. That
information is provided directly to Our third-party payment processors whose
use of Your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These
payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI
Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa,
Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the
secure handling of payment information.
Verifone
Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://www.verifone.com/en/us/legal
GDPR Privacy
Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data under GDPR
We may process Personal Data under the following conditions:
Consent:
You have given Your consent for processing Personal Data for one or more
specific purposes.Performance
of a contract: Provision of Personal Data is necessary for the performance
of an agreement with You and/or for any pre-contractual obligations thereof.Legal
obligations: Processing Personal Data is necessary for compliance with a
legal obligation to which the Company is subject.Vital
interests: Processing Personal Data is necessary in order to protect Your
vital interests or of another natural person.Public
interests: Processing Personal Data is related to a task that is carried
out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in
the Company.Legitimate
interests: Processing Personal Data is necessary for the purposes of the
legitimate interests pursued by the Company.
In any case, the Company will gladly help to clarify the
specific legal basis that applies to the processing, and in particular whether
the provision of Personal Data is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a
requirement necessary to enter into a contract.
Your Rights under the GDPR
The Company undertakes to respect the confidentiality of
Your Personal Data and to guarantee You can exercise Your rights.
You have the right under this Privacy Policy, and by law if
You are within the EU, to:
Request
access to Your Personal Data. The right to access, update or delete the
information We have on You. Whenever made possible, you can access, update or
request deletion of Your Personal Data directly within Your account settings
section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact Us
to assist You. This also enables You to receive a copy of the Personal Data We
hold about You.Request
correction of the Personal Data that We hold about You. You have the right
to to have any incomplete or inaccurate information We hold about You
corrected.Object to
processing of Your Personal Data. This right exists where We are relying on
a legitimate interest as the legal basis for Our processing and there is
something about Your particular situation, which makes You want to object to
our processing of Your Personal Data on this ground. You also have the right to
object where We are processing Your Personal Data for direct marketing
purposes.Request
erasure of Your Personal Data. You have the right to ask Us to delete or
remove Personal Data when there is no good reason for Us to continue processing
it.Request
the transfer of Your Personal Data. We will provide to You, or to a
third-party You have chosen, Your Personal Data in a structured, commonly used,
machine-readable format. Please note that this right only applies to automated
information which You initially provided consent for Us to use or where We used
the information to perform a contract with You.Withdraw
Your consent. You have the right to withdraw Your consent on using your
Personal Data. If You withdraw Your consent, We may not be able to provide You
with access to certain specific functionalities of the Service.
Exercising of Your GDPR Data Protection Rights
You may exercise Your rights of access, rectification,
cancellation and opposition by contacting Us. Please note that we may ask You
to verify Your identity before responding to such requests. If You make a
request, We will try our best to respond to You as soon as possible.
You have the right to complain to a Data Protection
Authority about Our collection and use of Your Personal Data. For more
information, if You are in the European Economic Area (EEA), please contact
Your local data protection authority in the EEA.
CCPA Privacy
Your Rights under the CCPA
Under this Privacy Policy, and by law if You are a resident
of California, You have the following rights:
The right
to notice. You must be properly notified which categories of Personal Data
are being collected and the purposes for which the Personal Data is being used.The right
to access / the right to request. The CCPA permits You to request and
obtain from the Company information regarding the disclosure of Your Personal
Data that has been collected in the past 12 months by the Company or its
subsidiaries to a third-party for the third party’s direct marketing purposes.The right
to say no to the sale of Personal Data. You also have the right to ask the
Company not to sell Your Personal Data to third parties. You can submit such a
request by visiting our “Do Not Sell My Personal Information” section
or web page.
The right to
know about Your Personal Data. You have the right to request and obtain
from the Company information regarding the disclosure of the following:
The categories of Personal Data collectedThe sources from which the Personal Data was
collectedThe business or commercial purpose for
collecting or selling the Personal DataCategories of third parties with whom We share
Personal DataThe specific pieces of Personal Data we
collected about YouThe right
to delete Personal Data. You also have the right to request the deletion of
Your Personal Data that have been collected in the past 12 months.
The right not
to be discriminated against. You have the right not to be discriminated
against for exercising any of Your Consumer’s rights, including by:
Denying goods or services to YouCharging different prices or rates for goods or
services, including the use of discounts or other benefits or imposing
penaltiesProviding a different level or quality of goods
or services to YouSuggesting that You will receive a different
price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or
services.
Exercising Your CCPA Data Protection Rights
In order to exercise any of Your rights under the CCPA, and
if you are a California resident, You can email or call us or visit our
“Do Not Sell My Personal Information” section or web page.
The Company will disclose and deliver the required
information free of charge within 45 days of receiving Your verifiable request.
The time period to provide the required information may be extended once by an
additional 45 days when reasonable necessary and with prior notice.
Do Not Sell My Personal Information
We do not sell personal information. However, the Service
Providers we partner with (for example, our advertising partners) may use
technology on the Service that “sells” personal information as
defined by the CCPA law.
If you wish to opt out of the use of your personal
information for interest-based advertising purposes and these potential sales
as defined under CCPA law, you may do so by following the instructions below.
Please note that any opt out is specific to the browser You
use. You may need to opt out on every browser that you use.
Website
You can opt out of receiving ads that are personalized as
served by our Service Providers by following our instructions presented on the
Service:
From Our “Cookie Consent” notice
bannerOr from Our “CCPA Opt-out” notice
bannerOr from Our “Do Not Sell My Personal
Information” notice bannerOr from Our “Do Not Sell My Personal
Information” link
The opt out will place a cookie on Your computer that is
unique to the browser You use to opt out. If you change browsers or delete the
cookies saved by your browser, you will need to opt out again.
Mobile Devices
Your mobile device may give you the ability to opt out of
the use of information about the apps you use in order to serve you ads that
are targeted to your interests:
“Opt out of Interest-Based Ads” or
“Opt out of Ads Personalization” on Android devices“Limit Ad Tracking” on iOS devices
You can also stop the collection of location information
from Your mobile device by changing the preferences on your mobile device.
“Do Not Track” Policy as Required by California
Online Privacy Protection Act (CalOPPA)
Our Service does not respond to Do Not Track signals.
However, some third party websites do keep track of Your
browsing activities. If You are visiting such websites, You can set Your
preferences in Your web browser to inform websites that You do not want to be
tracked. You can enable or disable DNT by visiting the preferences or settings
page of Your web browser.
Children’s Privacy
Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13. We
do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under
the age of 13. If You are a parent or guardian and You are aware that Your
child has provided Us with Personal Data, please contact Us. If We become aware
that We have collected Personal Data from anyone under the age of 13 without
verification of parental consent, We take steps to remove that information from
Our servers.
We also may limit how We collect, use, and store some of the
information of Users between 13 and 18 years old. In some cases, this means We
will be unable to provide certain functionality of the Service to these users.
If We need to rely on consent as a legal basis for
processing Your information and Your country requires consent from a parent, We
may require Your parent’s consent before We collect and use that information.
Links to Other Websites
Our Service may contain links to other websites that are not
operated by Us. If You click on a third party link, You will be directed to
that third party’s site. We strongly advise You to review the Privacy Policy of
every site You visit.
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the
content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will
notify You of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.
We will let You know via email and/or a prominent notice on
Our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “Last
updated” date at the top of this Privacy Policy.
You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically
for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are
posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, You can
contact us:
By email: info@scottsdalearts.orgBy visiting this page on our website:
https://scottsdalearts.org/contact/
Newsletter Sign Up
